Hi, I'm Kathleen, I lead the careers team at Udacity.
大家好 我是 Kathleen 我负责优达学城的就业辅助团队
We support students in their job search.
我们为寻找工作的学生们提供支持
The careers team knows what employers are looking for in a job candidate,
我们的团队了解招聘者在寻找什么样的求职者
and we want to work with you to market yourself as the best person for the job,
我们想和你一起努力 把你作为最佳人选推荐出去
whether it's a new role,
无论是新的工作
or a promotion at your current company.
还是在当前公司的晋升
You need to be proactive in your career development to be job-ready at graduation.
为了能在毕业时做好投入工作的准备 你需要积极参与你的职业发展规划
For this reason, career services are available throughout your Nanodegree experience.
正是因为如此 在你的整个学习过程中 你都可以获得就业指导服务
It's important to remember,
记住
while you're here to learn the technical skills for a job,
当你在这里学习相关工作技能的同时
it's equally important to know how to communicate
同样重要的一点 是明白
those skills to an employer through an application,
该如何向你的雇主展示这些技能
your online profiles, and in interviews.
你可以通过在线简历和面试来展示
Let's meet the careers team who will be with you along the way.
让我们来认识一下将会陪伴你们的就业团队
Hi I'm Rachel. Along with a network of career mentors,
— 大家好 我是 Rachel 我们团队和整个就业导师网络
our team is here to help you from when you begin to
都将会持续为你提供帮助
look for jobs until you accept your job offer.
从你开始找工作直至找到工作为止
Career support is present at different stages throughout your Nanodegree,
在你的整个纳米学位项目的不同阶段 就业支持会一直持续
and we encourage you to go through all of that
我们都鼓励你参与所有就业辅助内容
regardless of where you are in your job search.
无论你处于找工作的哪个阶段
Udacity career services include guides, lessons,
优达学城的职业服务包括指导、相关课程
and personalized feedback on topics like talking to recruiters,
和一些个性化反馈 范围包括 与招聘人员的交谈
interviewing, and optimizing your online profiles.
面试和优化你的在线简历
And I'm Trinh. In order to graduate career ready,
— 我是 Trinh 为了在毕业时完成进入职场的准备工作
you should continuously work on your career development.
你应该不断地完善你的职业发展规划
Like with all learning, beginning something earlier
就像其他内容的学习一样 越早开始就意味着
means you're more prepared when it's time to apply that learning.
当用到这些内容时 你的准备就越充分
When your dream job pops up,
当你的理想工作突然出现的时候
you want to be ready for it.
你所希望的是自己已经做好准备
We'll support you throughout your career development,
我们所提供的帮助 将会一直贯穿你的整个职业发展
on the forums, in career coach appointments,
通过论坛、就业指导预约
and through the career resource center.
和就业资源中心等方式
Hi I'm Kirsten, and I'm head of employer relations at Udacity.
— 大家好 我叫 Kirsten 我在优达学城负责雇主关系
Once you've completed the career curriculum,
课程完成时 你
you'll be ready to apply to jobs and talk with employers.
将会准备好申请工作和与雇主交谈
Udacity partners with industry leading companies,
优达学城合作伙伴中有行业领先的公司
who are looking to hire skilled and passionate people, like you.
他们都希望招聘到技艺精湛且激情四射的人 就像你这样
Having hiring partners means,
拥有招聘伙伴意味着
you'll have direct and preferential exposure at these companies.
我们能够直接且优先地将你推荐给这些公司
This will help give you a leg up in your job search as you explore your career options,
这将在你选择职业时取得优势
and develop a career path unique to you.
并为你开辟了一条独一无二的就业之路
Your passion, your location,
基于你的热情、所在地
and other career goals.
以及其他就业目标等综合因素
After you complete your first core Nanodegree projects,
— 在你完成纳米学位的首个核心项目之后
you'll then be prompted to begin your career development with us.
你将会和我们一起开始你的职业发展规划
We'll be there with you from then on as you explore your career options,
我们将一直与你同在 在你探索职业选择和追求梦想时
and pursue your dream role. We look forward to working with you.
我们期待和你一起携手并进